<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Galleries on cv19res</title>
    <link>http://cv19res.org/gallery/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Galleries on cv19res</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 22:25:02 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://cv19res.org/gallery/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>teach</title>
      <link>http://cv19res.org/gallery/teach/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 22:25:02 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cv19res.org/gallery/teach/</guid>
      <description>With the information gathered through our system, we can help people and communities to make informed decisions when faced with uncertainty regarding the current situation.
The information provided would allow for the minimization of movement restrictions through the distribution of people to the appropriate health care facilities without overloading them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>tech</title>
      <link>http://cv19res.org/gallery/tech/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 22:25:02 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cv19res.org/gallery/tech/</guid>
      <description>With the help of information and privacy technologies, we are able to inform governmental decision makers regarding the current COVID-19 pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>test</title>
      <link>http://cv19res.org/gallery/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 22:25:02 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cv19res.org/gallery/test/</guid>
      <description>Through a consortium of renowned research facilities and their combined efforts and expertise, we are able to increase the current amount of testing for the COVID-19 infection.
The information gathered from this testing will allow people and communities to quarantine more efficiently, accelerating the recovery of both the local economy and the well being of the population.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>track</title>
      <link>http://cv19res.org/gallery/track/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 22:25:02 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cv19res.org/gallery/track/</guid>
      <description>By collecting accurate anonymized data about the spread of COVID-19, we can better predict its evolution, thus allowing the local authorities and health care providers to be prepared for surges in infection while simultaneously keeping everyone&amp;rsquo;s privacy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>